<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Powershell on Ask Yammer</title>
    <link>https://askyammer.github.io/tags/powershell/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Powershell on Ask Yammer</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 05 Mar 2019 18:19:27 -0600</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://askyammer.github.io/tags/powershell/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Posting Message With Attachment via API</title>
      <link>https://askyammer.github.io/post/2019-03-05-posting-message-with-attachment-via-api/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Mar 2019 18:19:27 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://askyammer.github.io/post/2019-03-05-posting-message-with-attachment-via-api/</guid>
      <description>Posting messages to Yammer via API is a relatively simple process. When you want to add file attachments into the mix, things get more complicated as you have to utilize multi-part form data to post the message. I&amp;rsquo;ll be focusing on posting a message to Yammer with an attachment in a single API call. Keep in mind this method only supports attachments up to 25MB in size. If you need to post files larger than 25MB, you&amp;rsquo;ll need to use the Yammer web, desktop, or mobile clients for this.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Posting Message With Attachment via API</title>
      <link>https://askyammer.github.io/post/2019-03-07-posting-message-with-attachment-via-api/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Mar 2019 18:19:27 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://askyammer.github.io/post/2019-03-07-posting-message-with-attachment-via-api/</guid>
      <description>Posting messages to Yammer via API is a relatively simple process. When you want to add file attachments into the mix, things get more complicated as you have to utilize multi-part form data to post the message. I&amp;rsquo;ll be focusing on posting a message to Yammer with an attachment in a single API call. Keep in mind this method only supports attachments up to 25MB in size. If you need to post files larger than 25MB, you&amp;rsquo;ll need to use the Yammer web, desktop, or mobile clients for this.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>File Storage in Yammer</title>
      <link>https://askyammer.github.io/post/2019-02-28-file-storage-in-yammer/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Feb 2019 19:08:33 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://askyammer.github.io/post/2019-02-28-file-storage-in-yammer/</guid>
      <description>With our upcoming move to store Yammer files in SharePoint, we&amp;rsquo;ve received requests from admins to help audit the files currently stored in Yammer. While we don&amp;rsquo;t expect file storage quotas in SharePoint to be an issue, we understand that Yammer admins would like some additional clarity about how much file storage is being used in Yammer. The below PowerShell script will generate a .csv file showing how much data is stored in each Yammer group as well as the total of all files in the Yammer network.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Yammer API Primer</title>
      <link>https://askyammer.github.io/post/2017-09-05-yammer-api-primer/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Sep 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://askyammer.github.io/post/2017-09-05-yammer-api-primer/</guid>
      <description>While most day to day tasks can be accomplished in the Yammer web app, utilizing our APIs can open up administrative and automation options previously very time consuming. If you’ve never worked with an API before, this can seem like a daunting task. With this article, I hope to demystify APIs and illustrate how anyone can utilize them to perform tasks like obtaining, posting, and deleting messages.
Parts of an API call There are 3 main parts of an API call:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Find Office 365 users with Yammer licenses</title>
      <link>https://askyammer.github.io/post/2016-10-25-find-office365-users-with-yammer-licenses/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 25 Oct 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://askyammer.github.io/post/2016-10-25-find-office365-users-with-yammer-licenses/</guid>
      <description>Many times, we see customers that would like to know how many of their users have license for a specific Office 365 service. This post focuses on how to locate the users with Yammer licenses using PowerShell, it is based on this TechNet article: View account license and service details with Office 365 PowerShell with some changes regarding Yammer.
Before you begin The procedures in this topic require you to connect to Office 365 PowerShell.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>